<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>cthulhua</title>
 <link href="cthulhua.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="cthulhua.com/"/>
 <updated>2020-10-31T10:32:53-07:00</updated>
 <id>cthulhua.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Danny Hua</name>
   <email>danny.hua@hey.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Some idle thoughts on 'productivity'</title>
   <link href="cthulhua.com/2020/10/31/idle-thoughts-on-productivity"/>
   <updated>2020-10-31T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>cthulhua.com/2020/10/31/idle-thoughts-on-productivity</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For as long as I can remember I’ve had issues with so-called ‘productivity’, maybe more specifically, the idea that things are only worth doing as long as they’re productive. What ‘productive’ means, is a bit fuzzy. This manifests in different ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Feeling bad about enjoying my time doing fun things that don’t count as “productive”.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perfectionism, since I want my output at a task to be a certain quality.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Anxiety trying or learning new things I might be “bad” at.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are all a bit different, but I feel they’re related, and are something I’ve been working on for some time. In the past couple years I’ve tried to adopt a more….”just do it” mentality, and not be afraid of trying new things. This has worked pretty well in a few ways; I started running, hiking, lifting, and discovered I enjoy all those things, and can get better at them, I started learning piano, and am okay with the fact that I’m not very good at it yet, and I left a large tech company to work at an early-stage startup, something that I’ve been too risk-averse to do in the past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These new things have all mostly worked out, but I think a big part of this is allowing yourself to mess up, “waste” time, etc. That’s something I’m still working on, not beating myself up for not getting things perfect, or missing a work out, or for trying something out and being bad at it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
